At ICICI Lombard, we believe that
onboarding isn't just about joining a
company. It's about becoming part of a
family, embracing a shared vision, and
setting the stage for
success. Introducing Sakum, our
transformative gamified onboarding
experience that's changing the way new
employees connect with their roles and
our organization.
Your journey with Sakum begins with
creating your avatar, a personalized way
to represent yourself in the vibrant
virtual world of ICICI Lombard. Through
Saksham, new joiners embark on curated
learning journeys designed to provide a
deeper understanding of their role, the
company's philosophy, and the
opportunities that await them.
Welcoming you is Quarka, our friendly
guide who ensures your onboarding
journey is not just educational but
engaging and enjoyable. At ICICI
Lombard, our guiding philosophy, one,
one team fosters collaboration and
unity. Through Saksham, you'll explore
detailed insights into the behaviors and
values that make this philosophy a
reality. Meet our leadership in a
gamified interactive format. Understand
their vision and commitment to steering
ICICI Lombard toward excellence. Learn
the basics of insurance through real
life scenarios and puzzles. Making
complex concepts simple and easy to
grasp. Understand the essentials of HR
policies like the code of conduct,
working norms, leave policies, and
compliance topics such as
whistleblowing, posh, fraud, and IT
security. All in a gamified interactive
way. Our employees love Saksham. Here's
what they have to say. With a stellar
rating of 4.72 out of five, Sakam has
already made a lasting impression. It's
not just a game. It's a transformative
experience that immerses employees in
ICICI Lombard's world, preparing them to
contribute and
succeed. Saksham, empowering new
employees, enhancing engagement, and
building a future ready workforce.
Because at ICICI Lombard, we're not just
welcoming you, we're setting you up for
success.